A Guide to the James H. Latimer Papers, 1864-2000
Library of Virginia
- Photographs
  - "Le Lorgneur" - Antoine Watteau (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Libby, Margaret Randolph, Lt. (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Members and Officers of the Constitutional Convention of Virginia, 1901-02 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Mardan, Omar (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Miller, Francis Pickens, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous - courthouses, Mrs. Holton's Home, unidentified, Massive Resistance, Art Museum on wheels (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - National Political Figures - Nixon, Stevenson, Agnew, Ford (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - National Tobacco Festival, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Panoramic photograph, unidentified group (Map-case 8, Drawer 9)
  - Pickett, Owen (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Reynolds, Metals Company - Headquarters Building, 1958 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Robb, Chuck - Playing Tennis (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Communications Hall of Fame, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Virginia General Assembly ( Richmond Times-Dispatch photographs), 1972, 1973, 1975, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 8-11)
  - Virginia Supreme Court, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 12)